locallife.com 2001-08-16

# LocalLife Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Unisys is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible. Recognizing the growing concern over privacy on the Internet, Unisys adheres to a policy of full disclosure regarding the type of information obtained, how it is obtained, who uses it, how it is used and how customers can restrict the use of that data. The only information Unisys obtains about customers of, and visitors to, the locallife.net site is information supplied by the user for a specific purpose. As part of the Unisys Community Portal registration process, we ask for contact information and personal preferences (collectively “profile information”) that will help us customize the appearance of the web site to meet your needs. We may also occasionally ask for preferences during your visits to the site or during your attendance at online community events. While establishing your preferences is optional, a personal profile will help us serve you better.

If you are like most Web users, you’ve learned to be careful about providing personal information such as your e-mail or postal addresses. No one enjoys receiving unsolicited e-mail about subjects that are of no interest. **_You can rest assured that we will not share any personal information with another party without your explicit consent_**

The goal of locallife.com is to be your favorite destination on the Internet by providing you with the information, services and product offerings that are most relevant to you. Subscribing to the Unisys Community Portal Site provides you with access to all of the site’s information and features. The only information required is your name, e-mail address, credit card information, and mailing address. With your permission we may use your profile information to:

Occasionally, we will send you e-mail to notify you about important changes to the site, new Unisys services, and special offers from the Community. If you prefer not to receive this information, simply indicate this when you register for the Community or modify your profile information at anytime. 

With your permission, we may occasionally make your information available to specific merchants and other entities hosted on the Community Portal that provide products and services that seem to be oriented to your preferences. As a condition of hosting merchants and other entities on our site, Unisys requires these entities to comply with this Privacy Policy. We will never make your profile information available to anyone outside of Unisys or our merchants and other entities hosted on the Community Portal. 

While we will carefully comply with your elections for the distribution of profile information, we may collect and distribute aggregate statistics about Community Portal subscribers, traffic patterns, and related site information. These statistics will not include information that would identify any individual.

You will always have access to your profile information through the Community Portal Welcome Center and you will be able to change any of the information, including your preferences and information distribution elections. Should you choose to discontinue your subscription to the Community Portal, your profile information will continue to be protected under the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Unisys has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. Data you enter in the Community Portal Registration is encrypted with secure server software (SSL). Once the data reaches our site, it is protected by the same state-of-the-art security software we use to guard all of our company’s essential business data. Your profile information will be transferred to and stored on secured servers in the USA controlled by Unisys Corporation. Only authorized employees and contractors have access to the profile information you provide us and strict rules on Unisys employees and contractors who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every effort to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. Any other particularly sensitive information, such as your credit card number collected for a commerce transaction, is encrypted prior to transmission.

Whenever you surf the Web, an Internet Protocol (IP) address is automatically assigned to your computer. Web servers (the computers that host web sites) automatically identify your computer by IP address.

Unisys collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate or individual information to the Community Portal Merchants and other entities hosted on the Community Portal, and hosted advertisers, and to audit the use of the Unisys Community Portal Site. We don’t normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify you when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use, or to protect our site visitors or others. 

**How we use ‘cookies’**

In addition to the personally identifiable information that Unisys collects, we may also collect information anonymously using ‘cookies’. Presently ‘cookies’ play an important role in making the Internet work, but there is much confusion among Internet users about what cookies are and how they are used. A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the web site may identify you and track your activities on the web site. Although we believe that the use of cookies permits us to enhance your use of the Community Portal, most browsers permit you to disable the cookies function if you wish. The Community Portal may use ‘cookies’ to, among other things,

Store your user name and/or password so that you do not have to provide them at the time of entry.

Help merchants track business in their stores and process orders in individual shopping carts

Measure traffic patterns

Estimate audience size

Personalize content, banners and other promotions that you will see on the site

By registering for the Community Portal, you give Unisys your consent to process your profile information in accordance with the terms of this policy, including transferring your profile information to our servers in the United States where it will be stored in a database of Community Portal members. Only the information you have elected to provide during registration (at a minimum, your contact information) or visits to our web site will be processed.

**a. Privacy**

Unisys will not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information from a minor child without appropriate prior verifiable parental consent. You will be requested to, but shall not be required to, include information in your registration profile regarding the number of children in your household, their respective ages, and whether you consent to their use of the service. If you have agreed to allow your minor children to be registered as users of the Community Portal Service, you agree that you shall be solely responsible for: (a) the online conduct of such children; (b) monitoring the access to and use of the Community Portal Service by such children; and (c) the consequences of any use of the Community Portal Service by such children.

In the interest of protecting children, and in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998:

We will not collect personally identifiable online contact information from children under 13 without parental consent or notice which gives the parent the opportunity to prevent use of the information or the child’s participation. Without parental consent, such online contact information will at most be used to provide a direct, one-time response to a child’s request and nothing more.

We will not collect personally identifiable offline contract information for children under 13 without parental consent 

We will use legitimately gathered information from children under 13 years of age solely to provide them with access to services and content on the Community Portal and will NOT otherwise use or disclose such personally identifiable information without parental consent.

We have created a mechanism by which parents or guardians can review their children’s personal information, ask to have that information deleted, and refuse to allow any further collection or use of their children’s personally identifiable information.

We will not require children under 13 to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity as a condition of participation.

We will not entice children under 13 with the prospect of a special game, prize, or other activity to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

We will not give children under 13 the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information.

b. Access

Locallife.com links to sites outside of the Community Portal and also hosts third party sites (such as e-Stores) and interactive features (such as chat rooms), the content of which are not under direct control of Unisys.Specifically, Unisys does not control the content of the linked sites and, although Unisys has issued guidelines instructing hosted sites and chat room participants not to post offensive content, Unisys does not otherwise select or edit such content. Although children **under 18** will not be granted access to certain services, such as chat rooms, without parental consent, we advise parents and guardians to take advantage of additional measures to protect their children from exposure to inappropriate Internet content. 

**(2) Tips: **

First, parents should provide their children with common sense guidelines regarding safe use of the Internet. At a minimum, they should instruct their children NEVER to 

  1. share passwords with anyone. 
  2. give out personal information, including address, telephone number, parents’ work address and phone number, school location, photographs, etc., without parental permission. 
  3. respond to messages or solicitations that contain inappropriate content or that otherwise make the child feel uncomfortable, and to report such messages and solicitations to a parent. 
  4. agree over the Internet, to a personal meeting. 
  5. post inappropriate messages on the Internet. 

**(2)** **Tools:**

Second, there are a number of programs that allow parents to monitor, filter, restrict or otherwise limit their children’s access to the Internet. Among these are: 

Filtering tools

  1. CyberPatrol at www.cyberpatrol.com 
  2. Family Connect at www.familyconnect.com 
  3. iWay Patrol at www.iwaypatrol.com 
  4. Net Nanny at www.netnanny.com 
  5. SafeConnect at www.safeconnect.com 
  6. Surfpass at www.surfpass.com 
  7. Surfwatch at www.surfwatch.com 
  8. SOS Kidproof at www.soskidproof.com 
  9. We-Blocker at www.we-blocker.com 
  10. X-Stop at www.xstop.com

Monitoring devices

  1. Cyber Snoop at www.pearlsw.com 
  2. Cybersitter at www.cybersitter.com 
  3. ENUFF at www.akrontech.com 
  4. NetSnitch at www.netsnitch.com 
  5. We-Blocker at www.we-blocker.com

Pre-screened search engines and directories

  1. 4kids at www.4kids.org 
  2. Ask Jeeves for Kids at www.ajkids.com 
  3. Bess at www.bess.net 
  4. Children’s Internet Browser at www.chibrow.com 
  5. Electric SchoolHouse at www.electricschoolhouse.com 
  6. GO kids at www.go.com 
  7. Yahooligans at www.yahooligans.com

You should be aware that when visiting the Unisys Community Portal Site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. Specifically, when you click on links from the main site, hosted sites, e-Stores or advertisers, you may be exiting the Community Portal these other sites may send their own cookies and are governed by their own privacy policies. Likewise, although our hosted sites, e-Stores, and chat room participants are contractually obligated to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we do not continuously monitor the collection and use of information by those sites. Accordingly, Unisys is not responsible for privacy violations committed by hosted sites. If however, you become aware that a hosted site or chat room is violating this policy, kindly contact us through our Feedback Form. 

In other words, our policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet or your Internet Service Provider, and therefore beyond Unisys control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

Unisys may change any provisions of this policy at any time. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If at any time you believe that we have not adhered to any statement in our privacy policy or wish to discuss any issues related to our policy, please contact us through our Feedback Form. Your statutory rights are not affected.
